# ANIMASAUN DAVID

I specialize in crafting pixel-perfect websites from UI designs. My focus is on building responsive sites that provide an exceptional user experience and seamless functionality. Furthermore, I excel at working collaboratively, valuing communication and teamwork.

davidtimilehin739@gmail.com github.com/demoivre02 08029341783

# **Technologies and Languages**

- Languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript.
- Technologies: ReactJs, AngularJs, NextJs, Tailwind CSS, git, github, ChakraUI.
- Worked With: Vue js, ExpressJs, NodeJs, Gatsby, Graphql, firebase.
- Extras: PWA, Testing and Debugging, Team Collaboration, Performance Optimization

## **Experience**

#### July 2023 - present

### Otherfaces of tech - frontend engineer

- Managed and maintained the website by delivering new features and designs.
- Worked with developers and designers to ensure pixel perfect design.

November 2022 - July 2023

## CDLP Hub Ltd - frontend engineer

- Developed innovative JavaScript web technologies to build a user-friendly, adaptive, and responsive website with improved cross-browser compatibility and optimized runtime performance
- Led by the spearheading of a feature development project, the company's brand was reinforced through the creation of an appealing and captivating web layout for their destination website.

## september 2022 - November 2022

#### CDLP Hub Ltd - Frontend Engineer intern

- Utilized APIs to access data and integrate new functionalities into the application by communicating with servers.
- Collaborated with web designers to implement designs, layouts, and build user interfaces.

## Education

- Bsc physics University of Ibadan
- Fullstack web development Bootcamp Udemy

### Interest

- Open source
- Technical Writing